number one
zero the AG of5 years
old
number for example 1 million PES
coverage you can claim 1 million pesos
each
any of this critical
illnesses separate 20% minor critical
illness benefit so if 1 million PES
coverage you will receive an additional
of 200,000 pesos if diagnos minor
critical illness number three this will
also act as your life insurance so if
something happens to you your family is
protected and protected hospital bills
and this is Cash guaranteed
fible payment option between 5 years 10
years or even 20
years and there's a big
discount last but not the
least
illness on your third year the remaining
17 years wave premiums if you want to
learn more about the best health
insurance in the Philippines comment the
word how in the comment
section follow for more